Guide to the Center for Death Penalty Litigation Records, 1953-2020; 1953-ongoing and undated RL.00199
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Case Files Series, 1969-2006, 115 boxes
  - Willie Ervin Fisher, 1980-1999, 6 boxes
    - Habeas petition (Box 26)
    - Reasons for granting writ (Box 27)
    - Application for certificate of appealability (Box 27)
    - U.S. Supreme Court docs (Box 27)
    - Evidence (Box 27)
    - Transcript of evidentiary hearing, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Motion to reconsider denial of motion for appropriate relief (Box 27)
    - Petition for writ of certiorari information (Box 27)
    - Post oral argument developments (Box 27)
    - Petitioner's objection to magistrate order (Box 27)
    - Social history (Box 27)
    - Writ of habeas corpus documents (Box 27)
    - U.S. Fourth Circuit brief and reply (Box 27)
    - Press (Box 27)
    - Appendix to motion for appropriate relief, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Transcript of evidentiary hearing, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Memorandum opinion and final order (Box 28)
    - State bar v. David F. Tamer, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Trial transcript
      - Volume I, 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Trial transcript (Box 29)
      - Volume II, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Volume III, 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Volume IV (Box 29)
  - George Earl Goode Jr., 1992-2009, 5; 16 boxes
    In November 1993, George Earl Goode Jr. was convicted of the 1992 murders of Leon and Margaret Batten. Goode was indicted along with two others, Chris Goode, and Eugene DeCastro. DeCastro and Chris Goode were also convicted: Chris was sentenced to two life sentences, and DeCastro to death. George Goode was sentenced to death as well. Upon post-conviction appeals, Goode's defense argued that he had had inadequate legal counsel in his original trial; and that his attorneys had not adequately disputed the State's blood evidence. Goode's appeals counsel argued that though present, Goode did not actually participate in the murders. Moreover, they argued that the State misrepresented physical evidence to suggest that there was blood on Goode when there was no evidence of such. State Bureau of Investigation agent Duane Deaver, who claimed in trial that Goode had had the Battens' blood on him, subsequently came under scrutiny for mishandling and misrepresenting physical evidence in multiple criminal cases. A federal judge overturned Goode's death sentence in 2010, citing his ineffective trial attorneys, and sentenced Goode to two consecutive life sentences.
    - Trial Attorney (Lytch) files, 1992-1994; 11 folders (Box 134)
    - MAR hearing - uncorrected transcript, V1-V6, 2004; 7 folders (Box 134)
    - Trial Attorney (Lytch) files, 1992-1993; 3 folders (Box 135)
    - MAR hearing - uncorrected transcript, V7 -V13, 2004; 7 folders (Box 136)
    - Writ of Certiorari continued, Habeous Petition, 2004-2007; 19 folders (Box 136)
      Includes State's orders, objections, and notes and research
    - Habeas Corpus files, 2007-2008; 15 folders (Box 137)
    - MAR Hearing, April 2004, 1997; 15 folders (Box 137)
    - M. Montgomery files, 1994; 2004-2006; 18 folders (Box 138)
      Includes research files, mitigation investigation files
    - Trial transcript V0-V7, 1993; 12 folders (Box 138)
    - Trial transcript V8-V13, 1993; 9 folders (Box 139)
    - Main pleading, general correspondence, 1995-2004; 39 folders (Box 140)
      Includes correspondence with District Attorney's office, amendments to MAR
    - Post Conviction Hearing, 1992-1993; 2004; 42 folders (Box 141)
      Includes hearing prep notes, BB (Brenda Bissette) and DD (Duane Deaver) lab reports, "blood" references, notes, defendant's testimony at guilt and sentencing phase, Duane Deaver's testimony in Mike Peterson case, "sheriff's file"
    - 9/10/09 Oral Argument on Blood Spatter, Adams, Ineffective Assistance of Counsel(IAC) issues, 2008-2009; 44 folders (Box 142)
      Includes background research, lawyers' notes, mental health research on Adams; IAC - State v. Chapman and other cases
    - Laufer Work Files, 1998; 2 folders (Box 143)
    - Laufer - Newspaper Clippings, 1998 (Box 135)
    - Research files - Case Law and IAC, 1994-1997; 4 folders (Box 143)
    - SBI Naval Investigation, 1996 (Box 143)
    - Johnston County Sheriff Report, 1997 (Box 143)
    - Discovery Files from DA, 1992; (6 of 10); 10 folders (Box 143)
    - Discovery Files from DA, 1992; (4 of 10); 10 folders (Box 144)
    - Johnston County Superior Court, 1997; 2002; 4 folders (Box 144)
    - Reply, Affidavit, 1998 (Box 144)
    - Johnston County Superior Court, 1993; 3 folders (Box 144)
    - Voir Dire transcript, 1993; 2 folders (Box 144)
    - Motion to Disqualify, 1998; 3 folders (Box 144)
    - Investigation files (Savage and Laufler), 1992-2004; 12 folders (Box 144)
    - Discovery Pre Bares, 1992; 2 folders (Box 144)
    - Harnett County Supreme Court files, 1996; 4 folders (Box 145)
    - DNA Litigation files, 2004; 54 files (Box 145)
    - Chris Goode transcript, 1994; 4 folders (Box 146)
    - Chris Goode notes, Laufler's notes and files, 1996-1997; 34 folders (Box 146)
    - DeCastro transcript v11-13, 1996; 3 folders (Box 146)
    - Notes and To-Dos, 2004; 1 folder (Box 147)
    - Writ of Certiorari, 2004; 3 folders (Box 147)
    - Miller Continuance Motion, 2004; 1 folder (Box 147)
    - Affidavits, 1997-2004; 6 folders (Box 147)
    - Criminal Histories, 1987-2002; 2 folders (Box 147)
    - Witness Tampering Motion and Letters, 2004; 2 folders (Box 147)
    - Witness Direct Exams, 2002-2004; 12 folders (Box 147)
    - Photographs, 1992-1999; 7 folders (Box 147)
      Images depict scene of murder, including deceased persons
    - Judge Steve Balog Motion to Recuse, 2004; 1 folder (Box 147)
    - Discovery Motions, 2004; 4 folders (Box 147)
    - Patrick Byrd Records, 1987-2004; 9 folders (Box 147)
    - Motions and Orders for James Adams Records, 2004; 2 folders (Box 147)
    - Case Law, 1994-1998; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Writs and Briefs NC Supreme Court, 1997; 4 folders (Box 148)
    - Dirty Transcripts, 1994; 7 folders (Box 148)
    - Photographs, 1997; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - State of NC v. DeCastro, 1993-1997; 3 folders (Box 148)
    - Handwritten Notes, 1998; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Affidavits, 1997; 1 folder (Box 148)
    - Jury Information, 1994; 3 folders (Box 148)
    - Supreme Court Decision re: Discovery, 1998; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Discovery, 1997; 1 folder (Box 148)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, ca. 1996; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Attorney/Client Privilege Waiver, 1997; 1 folder (Box 148)
    - State Response to Cert Petition, 2006; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Transcripts of Prehearing Motions, 1997-2002; 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Corrected Transcripts of PC hearing, 2004; 14 folders (Box 149)
    - Cert and Post-Hearing Pleadings, 2005-2006; 11 folders (Box 149)
    - Order denying MAR, 2006; 4 folders (Box 149)
  - Harvey Lee Green, Jr., 1983-1999, 9 boxes
    Harvey Lee Green, Jr. was charged with two counts of murder for the 1983 killings of a Bethel, North Carolina store clerk and customer. Green was sentenced to death, but the North Carolina Supreme Court ordered a new sentencing hearing because jurors were prevented from considering mitigating evidence. Green was resentenced to death in 1992 and, after a series of failed appeals relating to the exclusion of African Americans on the jury, was executed on September 24, 1999.
    - Jury (Box 29)
      - Jurors excused/deferred (Box 29)
      - Jury instructions (Box 29)
      - Jury questionnaire (Box 29)
    - Jury questionnaire, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Jury list and selection (Box 30)
    - Expense sheet (Box 30)
    - Crime scene photo (Box 30)
    - State Bureau of Investigation lab report (Box 30)
    - Defendant's exhibits (Box 30)
    - Witnesses (Box 30)
    - Interviews, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Defendant's statements (Box 30)
    - Conference notes - client (Box 30)
    - Autopsy, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Psychological/psychiatric evaluation (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous records (Box 30)
    - Military records (Box 30)
    - Defendant's releases to attorney (Box 30)
    - Motions (Box 30)
    - Motions, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Case law, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Case notes and supplement (Box 31)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 31)
    - State's exhibits (Box 31)
    - Research notes (Box 31)
    - Draft of motion 15 (Box 31)
    - Subpoenas (Box 31)
    - State's case (Box 31)
    - Chargeable time slips (Box 31)
    - Attorney to-do lists (Box 31)
    - Opening/closing arguments (Box 31)
    - Department of Corrections files, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Appellate defender conferences (Box 31)
    - School records, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Social history (Box 31)
    - Fort Leavenworth records (Box 31)
    - Army records (Box 31)
    - Interviews
      - Individuals, 6 folders (Box 31)
    - Interviews (Box 32)
      - Individuals (Box 32)
      - Community leaders (Box 32)
      - Harvey Lee Green, Jr. (Box 32)
      - Friends (Box 32)
      - Family (Box 32)
      - Pitt County defense attorneys (Box 32)
    - Summary of records (Box 32)
    - Prior psychological evaluations (Box 32)
    - Releases (Box 32)
    - Prison achievements (Box 32)
    - Green's autobiographical statement (Box 32)
    - Judge's order denying relief (Box 32)
    - Federal discovery request - 11/6/1996 (Box 32)
    - Motion to N.C. Supreme Court to extend time - 6/26/1996 (Box 32)
    - State's memo and opposition to extend time (Box 32)
    - N.C. Supreme Court denial of time extension (Box 32)
    - Order setting execution date - 7/5/1996 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - execution date (Box 32)
    - Petition for NCSC writ of certiorari - 7/12/1996 (Box 32)
    - State motion to dismiss writ - 7/23/1996 (Box 32)
    - NCSC orders - 7/31/1996 (Box 32)
    - Pre-MAR funding pleadings, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Greenville news (Box 32)
    - News clippings - 1983 to 1992 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Contact list (Box 32)
    - Calendars from Administrative Office of the Courts (AOC) (Box 33)
    - Court martial (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous trial notes (Box 33)
    - Defendant's exhibits (Box 33)
    - Department of Corrections files (Box 33)
    - Educational records (Box 33)
    - Letters from Green (Box 33)
    - Autopsy photographs (Box 33)
    - Fees and expenses (Box 33)
    - Attorney notes
      - Conference with Tye (Box 33)
      - Harvey Lee Green, Jr. (Box 33)
      - Witnesses (Box 33)
    - Pitt County voter breakouts (Box 33)
    - Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Affidavits and records, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Jury information, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Jury research (Box 33)
    - Summaries of cases (Box 33)
    - Final copy of exhibits (Box 33)
    - SBI lab reports (Box 33)
    - Investigator's statement (Box 33)
    - Pitt County district attorney's staff (Box 33)
    - Case law
      - State v. Trent (Box 33)
      - State v. Plowden (Box 33)
      - State v. Newton (Box 33)
      - State v. Walks (Box 33)
      - State v. Mewborn (Box 33)
      - State v. Adams (Box 33)
      - State v. Warren (Box 33)
    - Case law (Box 34)
      - State v. Forbes (Box 34)
      - State v. Bazemore (Box 34)
      - State v. Sneed (Box 34)
      - Fletcher Hagan murder (Box 34)
      - Braswell case clippings (Box 34)
      - State v. Parker clippings (Box 34)
    - Newspaper searches (Box 34)
    - Batson litigation investigation (Box 34)
    - Dwayne Smith (Box 34)
    - Transcript - 7/24/1987 (Box 34)
    - N.C. Supreme Court record on appeal (Box 34)
    - N.C. Supreme Court motion submissions (Box 34)
    - Transcript - 5/8/1989 and 7/24/1989, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - McCleskey - Pitt County homicide case (Box 34)
    - McCleskey - summary of homicide data (Box 34)
    - Case law summaries (Box 34)
    - Juror notes (Box 34)
    - Pitt County jury information (Box 34)
    - Pitt County jury information (Box 35)
    - Pitt County population information (Box 35)
    - Affidavits, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Jury selection and composition (Box 35)
    - Jury documents (Box 35)
    - Pitt County voter breakouts (Box 35)
    - Case law
      - State v. Moore, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - State v. Braswell, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - State v. Parker, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - State v. C.J. Jones (Box 35)
      - State v. Thomas (Box 35)
      - State v. Hardy, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Notice and order (Box 35)
    - N.C. Supreme Court second addendum to record (Box 35)
    - Transcript digest (Box 35)
    - Motion for appropriate relief (Box 35)
    - Defendant's statements (Box 35)
    - State's response to writs (Box 35)
    - N.C. Supreme Court documents (Box 35)
    - U.S. Supreme Court documents (Box 35)
    - Petition for writ of habeas corpus (Box 35)
    - Exhibits, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - N.C. Supreme Court - defendant's brief (Box 36)
    - N.C. Supreme Court - supplemental brief (Box 36)
    - Order for date of execution - 8/1999 (Box 36)
    - Clemency (Box 36)
    - Affidavits (Box 36)
    - U.S. Circuit Court joint appendix, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - September 1999 appeals, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - U.S. Supreme Court - 9/1999 (Box 36)
    - Transcript excerpts (Box 36)
    - Second motion for appropriate relief, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - State court discovery litigation, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Fourth Circuit and U.S. Supreme Court, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - Zane Hill, 1987-1999, 5 boxes
    Zane Hill was convicted of the January 1990 first-degree murder of his son. Hill's lawyers argued that he was acting in self-defense and that the victim was wielding a pistol. Hill was sentenced to death and was executed on August 14, 1998.
    - Transcript - sentencing (Box 38)
    - Medical records, 9 folders (Box 38)
    - State's exhibits (Box 38)
    - Criminal history
      - Information (Box 38)
      - Printouts, 4 folders (Box 38)
    - Curtis Hill (Box 38)
    - Burglary and assault - 11/8/1989 (Box 38)
    - Arrest warrant - 1/1/1990 (Box 38)
    - Interview summaries - law-related professionals (Box 38)
    - Medical releases (Box 38)
    - Superior court documents (Box 38)
    - Court order regarding motion for appropriate relief (Box 38)
    - School records (Box 38)
    - Attorney-client motion (Box 38)
    - Motion for appropriate relief (Box 38)
    - Motion for appropriate relief court file (Box 38)
    - McDowall's notes: murder (Box 38)
    - Discovery from state (Box 38)
    - Motions (Box 38)
    - Defendant's sister, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Medical records (Box 39)
    - Correspondence and releases (Box 39)
    - Burglary - 11/29/1990 (Box 39)
    - Divorce - 1987 (Box 39)
    - Wrongful death - Randall Zane Hill (Box 39)
    - Murder documents (Box 39)
    - Kidnapping - 1/1/1990 (Box 39)
    - Kidnapping indictment - 1/1/1990 (Box 39)
    - Verdict templates (Box 39)
    - Character witnesses (Box 39)
    - Subpoenas (Box 39)
    - Motion for stay of execution - 7/10/1995 (Box 39)
    - Transcript - 9/27/1990 (Box 39)
    - Motion for appropriate relief - 3/2/1994 (Box 39)
    - State's answer to writ of habeas corpus (Box 39)
    - Administrative Office of the Courts memo on attorney fees (Box 39)
    - N.C. Supreme Court (NCSC) denial of writ of certiorari, 7/3/1995 (Box 39)
    - Stay motion and NCSC documents, 7/1995 (Box 39)
    - Stay orders - Judge Mullen (Box 39)
    - Trial transcript, 8/26/1994 - volume II, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - N.C. Supreme Court (Box 40)
      - Notes (Box 40)
      - Writ of certiorari (Box 40)
      - Opposition brief and reply - 1/1993 (Box 40)
      - Briefs (Box 40)
    - Order dismissing writ of habeas corpus - 3/31/1997 (Box 40)
    - Transcript - 9/19/1991, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Transcript errors and statement of case (Box 40)
    - Affidavit of indigency (Box 40)
    - Voluntary discovery and Brady v. Maryland (Box 40)
    - Warrant for arrest - 12/20/1989 (Box 40)
    - Commitment petitions (Box 40)
    - Direct/cross notes (Box 40)
    - Issues and recommendations as to punishment (Box 40)
    - Case law (Box 40)
    - Interview forms (jail) (Box 40)
    - Closing form (Box 40)
    - Transcript of plea (Box 40)
    - Appearance bond (Box 40)
    - Release orders (Box 40)
    - SBI final disposition report (Box 40)
    - Trial court file (Box 40)
    - Haywood County Hospital (Box 40)
    - Memorial Mission Hospital (Box 40)
    - Notes (Box 40)
    - Orders, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Petition for writ of habeas corpus (Box 40)
    - Respondent support for answer re: writ of habeas corpus and motion summary judgment (Box 41)
    - Defendant's exhibits, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Brief for state (Box 41)
    - Exhibits, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Trial transcript, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Trial transcript (Box 42)
    - Transcript - 9/27/1990 (Box 42)
    - 2008-0117-Disk 001: Motions (Box 42)
  - David Earl Huffstetler, 1983-1995, 5 boxes
    David Earl Huffstetler was convicted by a jury in Gaston County, North Carolina, for the first degree murder of his mother-in-law. Huffstetler had medical issues, many of which were deemed terminal by his physicians. He completed his first set of appeals through the state and federal courts, and filed a successor state motion for appropriate relief that was pending at the time of his natural death on September 15, 1995. Huffstetler's case file includes dozens of documentary videos.
    - Motion for appropriate relief (MAR) transcript, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Trial transcript, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - N.C. Superior Court motion for appropriate relief (Box 42)
    - Family photos, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Personal correspondence (Box 43)
    - Amended MAR (Box 43)
    - Background information (Box 43)
    - Will and medical records (Box 43)
    - N.C. Superior Court transcript, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - U.S. Fourth Circuit Court of Appeals
      - Brief of appellees (Box 43)
      - Brief of appellant (Box 43)
    - Motion for appropriate relief and amendments (Box 43)
    - Order - motion for appropriate relief (Box 43)
    - Petition for writ of habeas corpus (Box 43)
    - Appendix to writ of habeas corpus (Box 44)
    - Judgment - writ of habeas corpus and motion summary judgment (Box 44)
    - Oral argument (Box 44)
    - Transcript - motion summary judgment (Box 44)
    - Assorted legal documents, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - 2008-0117-Disk 004: David Earl Huffstetler data (Box 44)
    - Videos
      - 2008-0117-Video 005: #4 Window Dub, TRT 57:00, TC hr 6 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 006: #1 Window Dub, TRT 1:41, TC hrs 1,2 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 007: #7 Window Dub, TRT :29 min, TC hr 10 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 008: Legal Soundbite Bundle (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 009: #5 Window Dub, TRT 1:52, TC hrs 7,8 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 010: #7 Window Dub, TRT :29 min, TC hr 10 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 011: #2 Window Dub, TRT 1:37, TC hrs 3,4 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 012: #3 Window Dub, TRT :38 min, TC hr 5 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 013: #6 Window Dub, TRT :21 min, TC hr 6 (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 014: Legal Soundbite Bundle (Betacam) (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 015: Family History Bundle (Betacam) (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 016: Legal Soundbite Bundle (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 017: Legal Soundbite Bundle (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 018: Tape 1 Window Burn (Box 45)
      - 2008-0117-Video 019: Tape 2 Window Burn (Box 45)
    - Videos
      - 2008-0117-Video 020: Tape 3 Window Burn (Box 46)
      - 2008-0117-Video 021: #5 Window Dub TRT 1:52, TC hrs 7,8 (Box 46)
      - 2008-0117-Video 022: Tape 2 Window Burn (Box 46)
      - 2008-0117-Video 023: #3 Window Dub TRT :38, TC hr 5 (Box 46)
      - 2008-0117-Video 024: Legal Soundbite Bundle (Box 46)
      - 2008-0117-Video 025: Edit Master-Huffstetler Family History Bundle (BetacamSP) (Box 46)
      - 2008-0117-Video 026: Edit Master-Clemency Tape (BetacamSP) (Box 46)
      - 2008-0117-Video 027: Legal Soundbite Master (BetacamSP) (Box 46)
  - Joseph Timothy Keel, 1986-2003, 26 boxes
    Timothy Keel was convicted of the July 1990 first-degree murder of his father-in-law. Keel received the death penalty in part because of his previous conviction for the involuntary manslaughter of his infant son. Keel suffred from mental disabilities and had brain damage. The defense argued that the full extent of Keel's mental issues was not presented to the jury. After a series of appeals and reversals, Timothy Keel was executed on November 7, 2003. At 26 boxes, this case file is the largest in this collection and includes extensive information regarding Keel's mental health.
    - Motions and jury selection, volume I, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Motions and jury selection, volume II (Box 47)
    - Motion for imposition of life sentence, 1/31/2002 (Box 47)
    - Motion for appropriate relief (MAR), 1995 (Box 47)
    - Petition for writ of ceriorari, 3/28/2003 (Box 47)
    - Proportionality argument (Box 47)
    - Affidavit from juror (incomplete) (Box 47)
    - Governor correspondence, 10/16/2003 (Box 47)
    - United States Supreme Court (USSC) draft (Box 47)
    - Department of Corrections (DOC) releases (Box 47)
    - Summerlin v. Stewart (Box 47)
    - Fourth Circuit Court of Appeals successive cases (Box 47)
    - Writ of certiorari and motion to stay execution, 7/26/1999, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Case law (Box 47)
    - Trial transcript - 3/15/1993, volume V, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - In forma pauperis draft (Box 48)
    - 1994 appellate brief (Box 48)
    - MAR, 12/21/1995 (Box 48)
    - Affidavit of C.B. (Box 48)
    - Order from USSC, 8/21/2003 (Box 48)
    - Letter from C.W. re: destroyed files, 11/8/2002 (Box 48)
    - Affidavit of C.W. (Box 48)
    - MAR, 1/31/2002 (Box 48)
    - GED test (Box 48)
    - USSC - habeas corpus and stay of execution, 11/6/2003 (Box 48)
    - State responses to habeas corpus and writ of certiorari (Box 48)
    - Case law, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Writ of certiorari, 11/2003 (Box 48)
    - Respondent support of answer to habeas corpus and motion summary judgment, 2/15/1996 (Box 49)
    - Press (Box 49)
    - USSC docs, 11/6/2003 (Box 49)
    - Motion to file successive habeas corpus petitions, 10/13/2003 (Box 49)
    - Writ of habeas corpus and state's response, 10-11/2003 (Box 49)
    - Jury notes and interviews, 2003 (Box 49)
    - Clemency, 2003, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - MAR docs, 11/2003 (Box 49)
    - N.C. Lawyer's Weekly, 9/29/2003 (Box 49)
    - Photographs (Box 49)
    - Expert witness fee documents (Box 49)
    - North Carolina State Bureau of Investigation (SBI) file (Box 49)
    - Witness statements (Box 49)
    - Exhibits, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - SBI lab reports (Box 50)
    - Exhibits, 5 folders (Box 50)
    - SBI report, attachment 7 (Box 50)
    - Transcript digest (Box 50)
    - State v. Amy Keel (Box 51)
    - Witness statements (Box 51)
    - Evidence (Box 51)
    - Keel's polygraph, 9/2001 (Box 51)
    - Requests for files, 11/2001 (Box 51)
    - Amy Keel interview notes (Box 51)
    - Defendant's life and biography (Box 51)
    - Victor Keel medical records (Box 51)
    - The players, 7/1995 (Box 51)
    - Press (Box 51)
    - Trial transcript, 12/1986 (Box 51)
    - Interviews
      - Potential interview list (Box 51)
      - Interview summaries, 1995 (Box 51)
      - Interview summaries - family members, 1995 (Box 51)
      - Amy Keel's statements (Box 51)
      - Interviews with E.M. and D.K. (Box 51)
      - Interview summaries - trial/appellate counsel (Box 51)
    - K. H. file (Box 51)
    - Summary of attorney's files (Box 51)
    - C. W. notes (Box 51)
    - Victor Matthew Keel (Box 51)
    - State v. Keel, 1986-1987 (Box 52)
    - Psychologist/neuropsychologist (Box 52)
    - Interview with family (Box 52)
    - Newspapers (Box 52)
    - DOC records (Box 52)
    - Catalogues of documents (Box 52)